{
    "users": [
      {
        "email": "taylorlgulley@gmail.com",
        "username": "tlg",
        "password": "1234",
        "id": 1
      },
      {
        "email": "tlg@yahoo.com",
        "username": "Taylor",
        "password": "qwer",
        "id": 2
      },
      {
        "email": "meg@ducharme.com",
        "username": "megducharme",
        "password": "12345",
        "id": 3
      }
    ],
    "categories": [
      {
        "name": "James Bond",
        "userId": 1,
        "id": 1
      },
      {
        "name": "Boston Celtics",
        "userId": 1,
        "id": 4
      },
      {
        "name": "Harry Potter",
        "userId": 1,
        "id": 6
      },
      {
        "name": "Star Wars",
        "userId": 1,
        "id": 7
      },
      {
        "name": "Music",
        "userId": 1,
        "id": 8
      },
      {
        "name": "Something",
        "userId": 3,
        "id": 10
      },
      {
        "name": "Cuisine",
        "userId": 1,
        "id": 11
      }
    ],
    "questions": [
      {
        "categoryId": 1,
        "userId": 1,
        "question": "What is James Bond's codename?",
        "correct": "007",
        "wrong1": "006",
        "wrong2": "001",
        "wrong3": "004",
        "id": 1
      },
      {
        "categoryId": 1,
        "userId": 1,
        "question": "What was the name of James Bond's childhood estate?",
        "correct": "Skyfall",
        "wrong1": "Bond Manor",
        "wrong2": "Greenwich Estate",
        "wrong3": "It had no name",
        "id": 2
      },
      {
        "categoryId": 4,
        "userId": 1,
        "question": "What is Larry Bird's jersey number?",
        "correct": "33",
        "wrong1": "34",
        "wrong2": "32",
        "wrong3": "00",
        "id": 3
      },
      {
        "categoryId": 8,
        "userId": 1,
        "question": "Who is not a member of the Beatles?",
        "correct": "Pete Townsend",
        "wrong1": "Paul McCartney",
        "wrong2": "John Lennon",
        "wrong3": "Ringo Star",
        "id": 6
      },
      {
        "categoryId": 4,
        "userId": 1,
        "question": "How many championships do the Celtics have?",
        "correct": "17",
        "wrong1": "16",
        "wrong2": "18",
        "wrong3": "15",
        "id": 7
      },
      {
        "categoryId": 4,
        "userId": 1,
        "question": "Which was not a coach of the Celtics?",
        "correct": "Phil Jackson",
        "wrong1": "Doc Rivers",
        "wrong2": "Red Auerbach",
        "wrong3": "Brad Stevens",
        "id": 8
      },
      {
        "categoryId": 1,
        "userId": 1,
        "question": "Who makes Bond's gadgets?",
        "correct": "Q",
        "wrong1": "M",
        "wrong2": "Money Penny",
        "wrong3": "Himself",
        "id": 9
      },
      {
        "categoryId": 1,
        "userId": 1,
        "question": "What was the first Bond movie?",
        "correct": "Dr. No",
        "wrong1": "From Russia With Love",
        "wrong2": "Goldfinger",
        "wrong3": "Thunderball",
        "id": 10
      },
      {
        "categoryId": 1,
        "userId": 1,
        "question": "Who wrote the James Bond novels?",
        "correct": "Ian Fleming",
        "wrong1": "Agatha Christie",
        "wrong2": "Dan Brown",
        "wrong3": "Tom Clancy",
        "id": 11
      },
      {
        "categoryId": 6,
        "userId": 1,
        "question": "What is Harry's cousins name?",
        "correct": "Dudley",
        "wrong1": "Ron",
        "wrong2": "Hermione",
        "wrong3": "Draco",
        "id": 12
      },
      {
        "categoryId": 6,
        "userId": 1,
        "question": "What is Harry's owls name?",
        "correct": "Hedwig",
        "wrong1": "Fang",
        "wrong2": "Fluffy",
        "wrong3": "Aragog",
        "id": 13
      },
      {
        "categoryId": 6,
        "userId": 1,
        "question": "Which is the fourth book in the series?",
        "correct": "The Goblet of Fire",
        "wrong1": "The Prisoner of Azkaban",
        "wrong2": "The Order of the Phoenix",
        "wrong3": "The Deathly Hallows",
        "id": 14
      },
      {
        "categoryId": 6,
        "userId": 1,
        "question": "What is Snape's Patronus?",
        "correct": "A Doe",
        "wrong1": "A Stag",
        "wrong2": "A Serpent",
        "wrong3": "A Cat",
        "id": 15
      },
      {
        "categoryId": 6,
        "userId": 1,
        "question": "What creature is Dumbledore's faithful companion Fawkes?",
        "correct": "Phoenix",
        "wrong1": "Griffin",
        "wrong2": "Hippogriff",
        "wrong3": "Basilisk",
        "id": 16
      },
      {
        "categoryId": 7,
        "userId": 1,
        "question": "What year did Star Wars originally come out?",
        "correct": "1977",
        "wrong1": "1972",
        "wrong2": "1980",
        "wrong3": "1999",
        "id": 17
      },
      {
        "categoryId": 7,
        "userId": 1,
        "question": "What is the color of Luke's first lightsaber?",
        "correct": "Light Blue",
        "wrong1": "Red",
        "wrong2": "Green",
        "wrong3": "Purple",
        "id": 18
      },
      {
        "categoryId": 7,
        "userId": 1,
        "question": "Who gave Darth Vader his name?",
        "correct": "Darth Sidious",
        "wrong1": "Himself",
        "wrong2": "Yoda",
        "wrong3": "Obi-wan Kenobi",
        "id": 19
      },
      {
        "categoryId": 7,
        "userId": 1,
        "question": "What is General Akbar's famous line?",
        "correct": "\"It's a trap.\"",
        "wrong1": "\"Luke I am your father.\"",
        "wrong2": "\"Help me Obi-wan Kenobi you are our only hope.\"",
        "wrong3": "\"It's not wise to upset a Wookie.\"",
        "id": 20
      },
      {
        "categoryId": 8,
        "userId": 1,
        "question": "Who sang the song \"Little Red Corvette\"?",
        "correct": "Prince",
        "wrong1": "Michael Jackson",
        "wrong2": "Aretha Franklin",
        "wrong3": "John Mellencamp",
        "id": 21
      },
      {
        "categoryId": 8,
        "userId": 1,
        "question": "What famous singer is married to Diana Krall",
        "correct": "Elvis Costello",
        "wrong1": "Bruce Springsteen",
        "wrong2": "Michael Buble",
        "wrong3": "Harry Connick Jr.",
        "id": 22
      }
    ]
  }